{"items": [{"question": "An agreeable arousal", "answer": "Titillation", "options": ["adulation", "flattery", "Titillation", "compliment"], "answer_index": 3}, {"question": "A remark, expressing praise and admiration", "answer": "compliment", "options": ["proscribe", "flattery", "adulation", "compliment"], "answer_index": 4}, {"question": "Excessive or insincere praise", "answer": "flattery", "options": ["adulation", "flattery", "proscribe", "scribe"], "answer_index": 2}, {"question": "Servile flattery; exaggerated and hypocritical praise", "answer": "adulation", "options": ["scribe", "scribble", "proscribe", "adulation"], "answer_index": 4}, {"question": "Command against", "answer": "proscribe", "options": ["prescribe", "scribe", "scribble", "proscribe"], "answer_index": 4}, {"question": "Score a line on with a pointed instrument, as in metalworking", "answer": "scribe", "options": ["scribble", "prescribe", "describe", "scribe"], "answer_index": 4}, {"question": "Write\u00a0down quickly without much attention to detail", "answer": "scribble", "options": ["subscribe", "prescribe", "scribble", "describe"], "answer_index": 3}, {"question": "Suggest, order or authorize for use by a particular patient", "answer": "prescribe", "options": ["prescribe", "subscribe", "script", "describe"], "answer_index": 1}, {"question": "To give an account or representation of in words", "answer": "describe", "options": ["describe", "script", "subscribe", "scripture"], "answer_index": 1}, {"question": "Receive or obtain regularly", "answer": "subscribe", "options": ["manuscript", "scripture", "script", "subscribe"], "answer_index": 4}, {"question": "Something written by\u00a0hand", "answer": "script", "options": ["manuscript", "typescript", "script", "scripture"], "answer_index": 3}, {"question": "Any writing that is regarded as sacred by a religious group", "answer": "scripture", "options": ["subway", "scripture", "typescript", "manuscript"], "answer_index": 2}, {"question": "The form of a literary\u00a0work submitted for publication", "answer": "manuscript", "options": ["typescript", "subway", "manuscript", "subsurface"], "answer_index": 3}, {"question": "Typewritten matter especially a typewritten copy of a manuscript", "answer": "typescript", "options": ["subway", "inscribe", "typescript", "subsurface"], "answer_index": 3}, {"question": "An underground tunnel or passage", "answer": "subway", "options": ["subway", "inscribe", "postscript", "subsurface"], "answer_index": 1}, {"question": "Beneath the surface", "answer": "subsurface", "options": ["prescriptive", "subsurface", "postscript", "inscribe"], "answer_index": 2}, {"question": "Write, engrave, or print as a lasting record", "answer": "inscribe", "options": ["subscript", "postscript", "inscribe", "prescriptive"], "answer_index": 3}, {"question": "Textual\u00a0matter that is added onto a publication; usually at the end", "answer": "postscript", "options": ["postscript", "via", "prescriptive", "subscript"], "answer_index": 1}, {"question": "pertaining to giving directives or rules", "answer": "prescriptive", "options": ["prescriptive", "via", "obvious", "subscript"], "answer_index": 1}, {"question": "written or printed below the line", "answer": "subscript", "options": ["via", "obviate", "obvious", "subscript"], "answer_index": 4}, {"question": "By way of", "answer": "via", "options": ["obvious", "obviate", "via", "trivia"], "answer_index": 3}, {"question": "Easily perceived by the senses or grasped by the mind", "answer": "obvious", "options": ["trivia", "obviate", "militate", "obvious"], "answer_index": 4}, {"question": "prevent from happening", "answer": "obviate", "options": ["obviate", "trivia", "militant", "militate"], "answer_index": 1}, {"question": "Something of small importance", "answer": "trivia", "options": ["militancy", "militant", "trivia", "militate"], "answer_index": 3}, {"question": "be a powerful or conclusive factor in preventing.", "answer": "militate", "options": ["militia", "militancy", "militate", "militant"], "answer_index": 3}, {"question": "Engaged in war", "answer": "militant", "options": ["militant", "malign", "militia", "militancy"], "answer_index": 1}, {"question": "A militant aggressiveness", "answer": "militancy", "options": ["malignity", "militia", "militancy", "malign"], "answer_index": 3}, {"question": "civilians trained as soldiers but not part of the regular army", "answer": "militia", "options": ["militia", "malignity", "malignant", "malign"], "answer_index": 1}, {"question": "Evil or harmful", "answer": "malign", "options": ["malignant", "malignity", "malignancy", "malign"], "answer_index": 4}, {"question": "Wishing evil to others", "answer": "malignity", "options": ["malevolent", "malignity", "malignant", "malignancy"], "answer_index": 2}, {"question": "dangerous to health", "answer": "malignant", "options": ["malignancy", "malediction", "malignant", "malevolent"], "answer_index": 3}, {"question": "Quality of being disposed to evil", "answer": "malignancy", "options": ["maleficent", "malignancy", "malediction", "malevolent"], "answer_index": 2}, {"question": "appearing to wish evil", "answer": "malevolent", "options": ["malevolent", "maleficent", "malefactor", "malediction"], "answer_index": 1}, {"question": "calling down a curse", "answer": "malediction", "options": ["malefactor", "malediction", "maleficent", "maladroit"], "answer_index": 2}, {"question": "Harmful or evil in effect", "answer": "maleficent", "options": ["malaise", "maladroit", "maleficent", "malefactor"], "answer_index": 3}, {"question": "one who commits an offense", "answer": "malefactor", "options": ["malefactor", "maladroit", "malaise", "malicious"], "answer_index": 1}, {"question": "Not skilful or Quick", "answer": "maladroit", "options": ["malaise", "malicious", "maladroit", "malice"], "answer_index": 3}, {"question": "Physical discomfort", "answer": "malaise", "options": ["malaise", "malady", "malice", "malicious"], "answer_index": 1}, {"question": "intentionally harmful", "answer": "malicious", "options": ["malicious", "maladjusted", "malice", "malady"], "answer_index": 1}, {"question": "Feeling a need to see others suffer", "answer": "malice", "options": ["maladjusted", "malice", "malady", "malcontent"], "answer_index": 2}, {"question": "desperate condition", "answer": "malady", "options": ["maladjusted", "malcontent", "malpractice", "malady"], "answer_index": 4}, {"question": "poorly adjusted to demands", "answer": "maladjusted", "options": ["malcontent", "maladjusted", "malpractice", "malnutrition"], "answer_index": 2}, {"question": "dissatisfied with the existing state of affairs", "answer": "malcontent", "options": ["malpractice", "malcontent", "Titillation", "malnutrition"], "answer_index": 2}, {"question": "Professional wrongdoing that results in damage", "answer": "malpractice", "options": ["malnutrition", "Titillation", "compliment", "malpractice"], "answer_index": 4}, {"question": "A state of poor nutrition", "answer": "malnutrition", "options": ["Titillation", "flattery", "malnutrition", "compliment"], "answer_index": 3}], "title": "Word Power made Easy - Session 22.txt", "total": 45}